<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Health on 布萊德的學習網站</title>
    <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/tags/health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Health on 布萊德的學習網站</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 10:56:31 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bradleetw.github.io/tags/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Washington Post] &#39;No pain, no gain&#39; sounds tough, but you may only be hurting yourself</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/washingtonpost/nopainnogain_0919/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018 10:56:31 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/washingtonpost/nopainnogain_0919/</guid>
      <description>&amp;lsquo;No pain, no gain&amp;rsquo; sounds tough, but you may only be hurting yourself While training for a half-marathon last fall, Janet Sherman, 57, started noticing pain in her right leg and left foot. A diagnosis of a quadriceps strain and plantar fasciitis led to shoe inserts and cross-training. Before long, the Wyoming-based teacher was &amp;ldquo;just good enough&amp;rdquo; to get back to training, and so she did, although she opted to drop down to a shorter 10K race distance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Reuters] French baguette faces pinch from anti-salt lawmakers</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/reuters/frenchbaguette_0911/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 11:01:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/reuters/frenchbaguette_0911/</guid>
      <description>French baguette faces pinch from anti-salt lawmakers France&amp;rsquo;s beloved bread loaf, the baguette, may be about to lose some of its bite, with politicians looking into the health risks of additives set to propose legislation forcing bakers and processed food makers more generally to slash salt content.
After months of investigation and hearings, a parliamentary committee has come to the conclusion that voluntary agreements on the reduction of high salt levels have not been respected and that it is time to impose healthier norms via legislation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[The Guardian] The Guardian view on alcohol: drinking less is good for you</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/theguardian/alcohol_0910/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018 19:02:58 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/theguardian/alcohol_0910/</guid>
      <description>The Guardian view on alcohol: drinking less is good for you Alcohol is physically bad for you in any quantity; and the more you drink, the worse its health effects. The gigantic report on the subject published last week is unequivocal and authoritative. The report was based on enormous amounts of data: 28 million people around the world were examined in 592 studies to estimate the health risks.
The variety of ways in which alcohol can kill or damage people comes as a shock.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>