<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English on 布萊德的學習網站</title>
    <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/categories/english/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English on 布萊德的學習網站</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 10:12:29 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bradleetw.github.io/categories/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[Washington Post] The strange birth, death and rebirth of a Russian troll account called &#34;AllForUSA&#34;</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/washingtonpost/trollaccount_0823/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 10:12:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/washingtonpost/trollaccount_0823/</guid>
      <description>The strange birth, death and rebirth of a Russian troll account called &amp;ldquo;AllForUSA&amp;rdquo; An Indiana man named Jesse D. Allen created a website in 2005 with the title AllForUSA.com, apparently to pursue some business interests, but he soon abandoned the site. A decade later, at the age of 80, Allen died.
But AllForUSA was just getting started.
As the 2016 presidential campaign heated up, AllForUSA.com suddenly bristled with what appeared to be news articles celebrating Republican presidential nominee Donald Trump and bashing his Democratic rival Hillary Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[The Economist] Test-doctoring to keep Japanese women out of medical school</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/theeconomist/japanesediscrimination_0821/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 13:23:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/theeconomist/japanesediscrimination_0821/</guid>
      <description>Test-doctoring to keep Japanese women out of medical school Japan has made a lot of noise in recent years about demolishing the traditional view that women should stay at home while men go out to work. So it was shocking when, on August 7th, Tokyo Medical University, a prestigious medical school, confessed to marking down the test scores of female applications to keep the ratio of women in each class below 30%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Washington Post] Pentagon is moving toward estabilishing Trump&#39;s Space Force</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/washingtonpost/spaceforce_0820/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 14:18:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/washingtonpost/spaceforce_0820/</guid>
      <description>Pentagon is moving toward establishing Trump&amp;rsquo;s Space Force The Pentagon is moving toward fulfilling President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s request to establish a Space Force, in what would be the first new branch of the military in more than 70 years.
In a speech at the Pentagon Thursday at 11:15 a.m., Vice President Mike Pence is scheduled to lay out the administration&amp;rsquo;s plan. The Pentagon is also expected to release a Congressionally-mandated report on the issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Reuters] Apple breaches $1 trillion stock market valuation</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/reuters/applebreachesonetrillion_0816/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 13:55:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/reuters/applebreachesonetrillion_0816/</guid>
      <description>Apple breaches $1 trillion stock market valuation Apple Inc on Thursday became the first $1 trillion publicly listed U.S. company, crowning a decade-long rise fueled by its ubiquitous iPhone that transformed it from a niche player in personal computers into a global powerhouse spanning entertainment and communications.
&amp;ldquo;Financial returns are simply the result of Apple&amp;rsquo;s innovation, putting our products and customers first, and always staying true to our values,&amp;rdquo; Cook said in a memo to Apple&amp;rsquo;s more than 120,000 employees on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[New York Times] China&#39;s introverts find a kindred spirit: a stick figure from Finland</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/newyorktimes/chinaintroverts_0815/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 13:20:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/newyorktimes/chinaintroverts_0815/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s introverts find a kindred spirit: a stick figure from Finland People who live in China&amp;rsquo;s crowed cities are used to having their personal space invaded - in schools, malls, restaurants, bus stations, dormitories and even bathrooms. But that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean they like it.
Now a growing number of them identify with a Finnish cartoon character who channels their urban anxieties, albeit in a different cultural context.
The &amp;ldquo;Finnish Nightmares&amp;rdquo; comic series documents the social challenges faced by Matti, a mild-mannered stick figure who abhors small talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[MIT] Genetic genealogy is now solving recent crimes, not just cold cases</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/mit/geneticgenealory_0814/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 14:10:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/mit/geneticgenealory_0814/</guid>
      <description>. genetic:(a) [dʒɪ&amp;rsquo;netɪk] 基因的
. genealogy:(n) [dʒiːnɪ&amp;rsquo;ælədʒɪ; dʒen-] 族譜學; 血統
. genetic genealogy: 基因族譜學
. cold case: 懸案
For the first time, a public database of DNA profiles was used to solve a very recent crime. The implications for crime fighting are tremendous.
. implication:(n) [ɪmplɪ&amp;rsquo;keɪʃ(ə)n] 影響, 可能的結果; implication for sth: 對某件事帶來的影響
 This election has profound implications for the future of U.S. democracy. 对于美国民主的未来而言，这次选举影响深远.
What are the implications of these proposals?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[MIT] Therapists are augmenting eating-disorder treatment with virtual-reality headsets</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/mit/therapistswithvr_0808/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 12:41:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/mit/therapistswithvr_0808/</guid>
      <description>therapists:(n) [&amp;lsquo;θerəpɪst] 心理治療師; 臨床醫學家
 augmenting:(v) [ɔ:g&amp;rsquo;mentiŋ] 增強; 加強
 He has to find work to augment his income.
 eating-disorder: 飲食失調
 treatment:(n) [&amp;lsquo;triːtm(ə)nt] 療法
 The best treatment for a cold is to rest and drink lots of fluids. 治疗感冒的最佳方法是休息和多喝水.
  Though most consumers aren&amp;rsquo;t yet sure what to do with VR, some psychologists are using it to treat anorexia and bulimia.
 psychologists:(n) [saɪ&amp;rsquo;kɒlədʒɪst] 心理學家</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump blasts back after Times publisher decries &#39;enemy of the people&#39; attacks</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/theguardian/trumpnews_0807/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 14:19:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/theguardian/trumpnews_0807/</guid>
      <description>. blast back:(v) 猛烈回擊 { blast:(v) 爆炸 }
. decry:(v) 譴責
Hours after saying he had a &amp;ldquo;very good meeting&amp;rdquo; with the publisher of the New York Times about his labelling the press the &amp;ldquo;enemy of the people&amp;rdquo;, Donald Trump launched a blistering attack on &amp;ldquo;anti-Trump haters in the dying newspaper industry&amp;rdquo;.
. blistering:(a) 猛烈的; 嚴厲的; 無情的
. hater:(n) 懷恨者
. dying:(a) 垂死的
&amp;ldquo;The failing New York Times and the Amazon Washington Post do nothing but write bad stories even on very positive achievements,&amp;rdquo; Trump tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>