<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on 布萊德的學習網站</title>
    <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on 布萊德的學習網站</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 11:37:18 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bradleetw.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful URL</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/usefulurl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 11:37:18 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/usefulurl/</guid>
      <description>Machine Learning ◻️Foundations of machine learning, from Bloomberg ML EDU: Understand the Concepts, Techniques and Mathematical Frameworks Used by Experts in Machine Learning
◻️Seed Bank
◻️100 Days of ML Code
◻️How decision tree work
◻️Python codes for common Machine Learning Algorithms
◻️&amp;ldquo;Diving deeper into Reinforcement Learning with Q-Learning&amp;rdquo;
◻️&amp;ldquo;An introduction to Deep Q-Learning: let’s play Doom&amp;rdquo;
◻️&amp;ldquo;Improvements in Deep Q Learning: Dueling Double DQN, Prioritized Experience Replay, and fixed Q-targets&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Machine Learning] Resources for CS229 - Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/machinelearning/stanford_cheatsheet_0826/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 21:56:50 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/machinelearning/stanford_cheatsheet_0826/</guid>
      <description>https://stanford.edu/~shervine/teaching/cs-229.html
一位使丹佛大學的 Data Science track of the Computational and Mathematical Engineering department 研究生, Shervine, 在 Machine learning 的課程中所準備的相關資料.
Probabilities and Statistics refresher Linear Algebra and Calculus refresher Deep Learning cheatsheet Supervised Learning cheatsheet Unsupervised Learning cheatsheet Machine Learning tips and tricks cheatsheet https://github.com/afshinea/stanford-cs-229-machine-learning</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Reuters] FBI seeks motive after U.S. airline worker steals plane, crashes it</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/reuters/alaskaairlines_0826/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2018 12:02:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/reuters/alaskaairlines_0826/</guid>
      <description>FBI seeks motive after U.S. airline worker steals plane, crashes it A Horizon Air ground service agent got into a Bombardier Q400 turboprop aircraft on Friday night in a maintenance area at Seattle-Tacoma International Airport and took off, Horizon sister carrier Alaska Airlines said.
He flew for about one hour, often erratically with attempts at aerial stunts, before crashing onto sparsely populated Ketron Island in Puget Sound, some 25 miles to the southwest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[New York Times] V.S. Naipaul, who explored colonialism through unsparing books, dies at 85</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/newyorktimes/naipaul_0825/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2018 12:00:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/newyorktimes/naipaul_0825/</guid>
      <description>V.S. Naipaul, who explored colonialism through unsparing books, dies at 85 V.S. Naipaul, the Nobel laureate who documented the migrations of peoples, the unraveling of the British Empire, the ironies of exile and the clash between belief and unbelief in more than a dozen unsparing novels and as manay works of nonfiction, died Saturday at his home in Londaon. He was 85.
His family confirmed the death in a statement, The Associated Press reported.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[BBC News] Elon Musk is playing a dangerous game</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/bbcnews/elonmusk_0824/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 14:52:34 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/bbcnews/elonmusk_0824/</guid>
      <description>Elon Musk is playing a dangerous game There is never a dull moment with the mercurial Mr Musk, but he excelled himself on Tuesday, stunning the markets by tweeting that he was considering taking the company private by buying publicly available shares for $420 each - a significant premium to the $340 they were trading at before he dropped his bombshell.
If it turns out his Twitter promise - that he has secured the tens of billions of dollars he would need to buy out public shareholders - is in any way shaky, then he could find himself accused of price manipulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Washington Post] The strange birth, death and rebirth of a Russian troll account called &#34;AllForUSA&#34;</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/washingtonpost/trollaccount_0823/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 10:12:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/washingtonpost/trollaccount_0823/</guid>
      <description>The strange birth, death and rebirth of a Russian troll account called &amp;ldquo;AllForUSA&amp;rdquo; An Indiana man named Jesse D. Allen created a website in 2005 with the title AllForUSA.com, apparently to pursue some business interests, but he soon abandoned the site. A decade later, at the age of 80, Allen died.
But AllForUSA was just getting started.
As the 2016 presidential campaign heated up, AllForUSA.com suddenly bristled with what appeared to be news articles celebrating Republican presidential nominee Donald Trump and bashing his Democratic rival Hillary Clinton.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Julia Language</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/julia/julia_0812/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 16:27:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/julia/julia_0812/</guid>
      <description>MIT 开发的 Julia 语言是全球热度上升最快的编程语言之一，下载量超过 200 万次，下载者包括谷歌、Facebook、FAA 和美国能源部等各个部门的开发者。近日，MIT CSAIL 实验室正式发布了 Julia 1.0，该语言期望结合 C 的速度、Matlab 的数学表征、Python 的通用编程与 Shell 的胶水命令行，并构建开源、自由与便捷的编程语言。
Julia 的特點, 參考Julia 1.0, 節錄其中一段:  快速：Julia 一開始就是為高效能設計的。 Julia 可以藉由 LLVM 被編譯成不同平台的高效機器碼。   LLVM: 可參考[LLVM每日谈之一 LLVM是什么]. 節錄其中一段, &amp;ldquo;LLVM 的主要作用是它可以作为多种语言的后端，它可以提供可编程语言无关的优化和针对很多种CPU的代码生成功能&amp;rdquo;.
  泛用：Julia 使用多重分派（multiple dispatch）作為程式典範（paradigm），可以更容易表達物件導向和函數-式的設計模式。標準函式庫提供了非同步 I/O，行程控制，日誌記錄，效能分析，套件管理器等等。
 動態：Julia 是動態型別的，用起來像腳本語言，並且很好地支援互動式的操作方式。
 技術：Julia 擅長數值運算，有非常貼近數學的語法，支援多種數值型別，並且支援平行運算。Julia 的多重分派結合數值和陣列相關的資料型別可以說是渾然天成。
 選擇性的型別標註：Julia 有豐富的資料型別描述，型別宣告可以使得程式更加清楚和穩固。
 組合性：Julia 的套件可以很和諧的一起運作。矩陣的單位數量或是資料表中一行的貨幣和顏色可以一起運作並且擁有良好的效能。
  這個新的語言能作什麼, 目前還說不上, 只知道這是個從 MIT 出來, 集大家需求而生的一個開源新語言, 不想掉隊, 只有先學再說了.
目前先從 2 個線上的資源開始</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[The Economist] Test-doctoring to keep Japanese women out of medical school</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/theeconomist/japanesediscrimination_0821/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 13:23:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/theeconomist/japanesediscrimination_0821/</guid>
      <description>Test-doctoring to keep Japanese women out of medical school Japan has made a lot of noise in recent years about demolishing the traditional view that women should stay at home while men go out to work. So it was shocking when, on August 7th, Tokyo Medical University, a prestigious medical school, confessed to marking down the test scores of female applications to keep the ratio of women in each class below 30%.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Washington Post] Pentagon is moving toward estabilishing Trump&#39;s Space Force</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/washingtonpost/spaceforce_0820/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Aug 2018 14:18:53 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/washingtonpost/spaceforce_0820/</guid>
      <description>Pentagon is moving toward establishing Trump&amp;rsquo;s Space Force The Pentagon is moving toward fulfilling President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s request to establish a Space Force, in what would be the first new branch of the military in more than 70 years.
In a speech at the Pentagon Thursday at 11:15 a.m., Vice President Mike Pence is scheduled to lay out the administration&amp;rsquo;s plan. The Pentagon is also expected to release a Congressionally-mandated report on the issue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Reuters] Apple breaches $1 trillion stock market valuation</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/reuters/applebreachesonetrillion_0816/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 13:55:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/reuters/applebreachesonetrillion_0816/</guid>
      <description>Apple breaches $1 trillion stock market valuation Apple Inc on Thursday became the first $1 trillion publicly listed U.S. company, crowning a decade-long rise fueled by its ubiquitous iPhone that transformed it from a niche player in personal computers into a global powerhouse spanning entertainment and communications.
&amp;ldquo;Financial returns are simply the result of Apple&amp;rsquo;s innovation, putting our products and customers first, and always staying true to our values,&amp;rdquo; Cook said in a memo to Apple&amp;rsquo;s more than 120,000 employees on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[New York Times] China&#39;s introverts find a kindred spirit: a stick figure from Finland</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/newyorktimes/chinaintroverts_0815/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 13:20:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/newyorktimes/chinaintroverts_0815/</guid>
      <description>China&amp;rsquo;s introverts find a kindred spirit: a stick figure from Finland People who live in China&amp;rsquo;s crowed cities are used to having their personal space invaded - in schools, malls, restaurants, bus stations, dormitories and even bathrooms. But that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean they like it.
Now a growing number of them identify with a Finnish cartoon character who channels their urban anxieties, albeit in a different cultural context.
The &amp;ldquo;Finnish Nightmares&amp;rdquo; comic series documents the social challenges faced by Matti, a mild-mannered stick figure who abhors small talk.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[MIT] Genetic genealogy is now solving recent crimes, not just cold cases</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/mit/geneticgenealory_0814/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 14:10:30 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/mit/geneticgenealory_0814/</guid>
      <description>. genetic:(a) [dʒɪ&amp;rsquo;netɪk] 基因的
. genealogy:(n) [dʒiːnɪ&amp;rsquo;ælədʒɪ; dʒen-] 族譜學; 血統
. genetic genealogy: 基因族譜學
. cold case: 懸案
For the first time, a public database of DNA profiles was used to solve a very recent crime. The implications for crime fighting are tremendous.
. implication:(n) [ɪmplɪ&amp;rsquo;keɪʃ(ə)n] 影響, 可能的結果; implication for sth: 對某件事帶來的影響
 This election has profound implications for the future of U.S. democracy. 对于美国民主的未来而言，这次选举影响深远.
What are the implications of these proposals?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[MIT] Therapists are augmenting eating-disorder treatment with virtual-reality headsets</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/mit/therapistswithvr_0808/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Aug 2018 12:41:59 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/mit/therapistswithvr_0808/</guid>
      <description>therapists:(n) [&amp;lsquo;θerəpɪst] 心理治療師; 臨床醫學家
 augmenting:(v) [ɔ:g&amp;rsquo;mentiŋ] 增強; 加強
 He has to find work to augment his income.
 eating-disorder: 飲食失調
 treatment:(n) [&amp;lsquo;triːtm(ə)nt] 療法
 The best treatment for a cold is to rest and drink lots of fluids. 治疗感冒的最佳方法是休息和多喝水.
  Though most consumers aren&amp;rsquo;t yet sure what to do with VR, some psychologists are using it to treat anorexia and bulimia.
 psychologists:(n) [saɪ&amp;rsquo;kɒlədʒɪst] 心理學家</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Git]如何忽略追蹤特定檔案或目錄?</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/developmenttools/gitstudy/gitrelated_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 11:49:49 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/developmenttools/gitstudy/gitrelated_1/</guid>
      <description>只要編輯以下三個檔案(忽略清單)其中一個就可以忽略追蹤特定檔案或目錄:
 $HOME/.config/git/ignore: 開發者電腦中的所有倉庫都可以讀取該忽略清單. .gitignore: 每個倉庫都有自己一份的忽略清單放在該倉庫根目錄下, 而且該忽略清單可以被分享追蹤管理. .git/info/exclude: 該忽略清單無法被追蹤管理.  $HOME/.config/git/ignore 有時候系統或者一些第三方應用為了讓其運作的效果更好, 會在目錄底下產生一些額外的檔案, 列如: .DS_Store, 而這些對開發者本身而言這類無關開發的資料都是不必要去追蹤紀錄, 這時可以透過編輯 $HOME/.config/git/ignore 來寫下要忽略的檔案, 而這個是對系統內的所有倉庫都有用. 以下是該檔案內的一些範例:
# General .DS_Store .AppleDouble .LSOverride # Files that might appear in the root of a volume .DocumentRevisions-V100 .fseventsd .Spotlight-V100 .TemporaryItems .Trashes .VolumeIcon.icns .com.apple.timemachine.donotpresent  .gitignore 在開發的環境中會因為編譯產生執行檔案, 連結檔, 某些檔案或是某些目錄開發者根本不必追蹤, 但是這個忽略清單卻是可以分享給其他開發者或者需要版本管控忽略清單 (有可能在經過一段的開發時間, 開發環境導入了新的機制或是功能, 而產生新的不必追蹤檔案) 這時只要在開發項目的根目錄下放入 .gitignore, 在該檔案中寫入你要忽略上傳的特定檔案或目錄:
 特定檔案: 直接放入檔案名稱, ex: somefolder/specific.txt
 符合特定字串的檔案: 加入萬用字元, ex: /db/*.sqlite3
 目錄: ex: somefolder/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump blasts back after Times publisher decries &#39;enemy of the people&#39; attacks</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/theguardian/trumpnews_0807/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 14:19:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/theguardian/trumpnews_0807/</guid>
      <description>. blast back:(v) 猛烈回擊 { blast:(v) 爆炸 }
. decry:(v) 譴責
Hours after saying he had a &amp;ldquo;very good meeting&amp;rdquo; with the publisher of the New York Times about his labelling the press the &amp;ldquo;enemy of the people&amp;rdquo;, Donald Trump launched a blistering attack on &amp;ldquo;anti-Trump haters in the dying newspaper industry&amp;rdquo;.
. blistering:(a) 猛烈的; 嚴厲的; 無情的
. hater:(n) 懷恨者
. dying:(a) 垂死的
&amp;ldquo;The failing New York Times and the Amazon Washington Post do nothing but write bad stories even on very positive achievements,&amp;rdquo; Trump tweeted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Hugo]建立固定格式的新帖子</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/web/staticsitegenerator/hugo/posttemplate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Aug 2018 13:09:33 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/web/staticsitegenerator/hugo/posttemplate/</guid>
      <description>創建固定欄位的 Markdown 檔案 當使用者在一般的文書編輯器要開始創立 Markdown 新文章時, 除了透過該編輯器的 new file 外, 好像就沒有其他方法, 而這種方式只能產生一個空的檔案. 所以我們目前只能用 command line 來透過 $ hugo new newPostFile.md 的命令來產生新的 markdown 文章, 而且該文章會自動生成固定的欄位, 方便使用者寫作.
為什麼要透過這種方式來創建 Markdown 文章 透過這種方式, 使用者可以事先將 Markdown 文章常用到的 metadata 的欄位或者該欄位的值放到特定檔案, 在創建新 Markdown 文章時就能預設有這些欄位, 節省使用者寫作時間.
修改 default.md 當使用者透過 $ hugo new newPostFile.md 時, Hugo 會到該 Hugo project 底下的 archetypes 目錄找尋 default.md, 依據其內容而在新的 Markdown 檔案產生相對的欄位. 一般來說在 GitHub 上所公開的模板可能也會附上相對的 default.md (其實很多也都沒附上), 使用者只要下載該模板後, 到該模板的目錄下找 archetypes 就可以發現.
透過 $ hugo new site newProject 產生網站時, 會生成 default.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>讓 iTerm2 有很酷炫的外表!</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/developmenttools/iterm2setting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 17:41:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/developmenttools/iterm2setting/</guid>
      <description>常看到電影裡的駭客在操作電腦時所用的 command line 都是那麼的酷, 今天就來速記一下參考網路上別人分享設定的步驟. 參考的來源: 超簡單！十分鐘打造漂亮又好用的 zsh command line 環境
iTerm2 的安裝就沒記錄, 因為早就安裝過, 安裝流程也不難.
安裝 zsh + oh-my-zsh zsh 是類似 bash, 在一般的使用上兩者差不多, 而 zsh 要再搭配上 oh-my-zsh(它是基於 zsh 的一個擴展工具集, 提供了豐富的擴展功能), 就可以設置有趣的主題風格(Themes), 而 oh-my-zsh 本身就提供了很多主題可以讓你挑選.
 安裝 zsh:
$ brew install zsh  將 zsh 改成預設 shell:
$ sudo sh -c &amp;quot;echo $(which zsh) &amp;gt;&amp;gt; /etc/shells&amp;quot; $ chsh -s $(which zsh)  安裝 oh-my-zsh:
$ wget https://github.com/robbyrussell/oh-my-zsh/raw/master/tools/install.sh $ bash ./install.sh   安裝 zsh theme: powerlevel9k  下載好用的主題:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>如何利用 GitHub Pages 建立博客?</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/web/deployment/githubblog/usegithub_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2018 14:31:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/web/deployment/githubblog/usegithub_1/</guid>
      <description>什麼是 GitHub Pages(blog)? 在大家的印象中 GitHub 只是一個利用 git 讓大家免費放代碼, 追蹤 issues , 和各地好手討論的地方. 某天看到ㄧ篇文章的 URL 很特別, 是 https://xxxxxx.github.io/ , 和我平常看 GitHub 的 https://github.com 很像, 後來才知道 GitHub 可以讓使用者在上面放 blog(有空還是要看看人家的 &amp;ldquo;Read the guide&amp;rdquo;), 重點是&amp;rdquo;不用錢&amp;rdquo;(廢話, 不過被微軟買掉後會不會調整, 就不知了).
refer to: What is GitHub Pages?
為什麼要使用 GitHub 來架設 blog? 在嘗試 GitHub 架設 blog 之前, 我正在學習使用 Google Cloud platfrom 試著架設 blog 網站, 自己申請域名, 申請 SSL, 突然想起 GitHub 上也有 blog 功能而且我也還沒試過, 查了一下, 還蠻容易設定的, 而且省去申請域名, SSL, 不用擔心服務器防火牆的相關問題, 當然你必須要有 GitHub 帳號(廢話 ~).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>透過調整 config.toml 設定 Hugo 網站(1)</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/web/staticsitegenerator/hugo/usehugo_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 15:10:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/web/staticsitegenerator/hugo/usehugo_2/</guid>
      <description>透過合適的模板來學習調整 Hugo 網站 一般來說在 GitHub 上的每一個模板除了使用說明檔(Readme.md)之外, 也會附上如何使用的範例, 例如你可以在 themes/ananke/exampleSite (ananke 換成你所下載的模板名稱)中看到相關的使用範例, 透過這些也可以很快上手 Hugo 網站的調整設定. 不過我也下載過很多沒附上 exampleSite 的模板, 而且Readme.md 也不是寫給初學者看的, 造成學習上的難度. 所以初學者挑選學習的模板請謹慎. 官方 Quick start 中所用的模板 ananke 就涵蓋這些資料.
config.toml Hugo 網站主要是透過 config.toml 這個檔案來調控, 當你透過 $ hugo new site YourWebSite 建立空網站時 Hugo 就幫你建立一個 config.toml (也支持 yaml 和 json 格式, 預設是 toml 格式).
直接先用所下載模板提供的 config.toml, themes/ananke/exampleSite/config.toml 取代原本 config.toml, 了解一下模板的 README.md, 再來更改相關的欄位.
 先移除 themesDir = &amp;quot;../..&amp;quot; 這行.
 title = &amp;ldquo;Your new Hugo Site Title&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>使用Hugo產生靜態網頁</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/web/staticsitegenerator/hugo/usehugo_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Jul 2018 12:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/web/staticsitegenerator/hugo/usehugo_1/</guid>
      <description>為什麼要用靜態網頁產生器(Static Site Generators)? 靜態網頁產生器一般都會有很多現成的模板(template), 只要相關設定正確, 使用者只要專心編寫你的內容即可(但只要你有強迫症, 可能就會想要自己調整更多的細節).
原本我不知有這類的工具, 是因為在學習別的項目時看到別人的文章, 只用一兩句話描述說可以用Hugo很快產生網頁, 只要上網查找學習就可以, 然後我就上當了&amp;hellip;
靜態網頁產生器這類工具確實可以很快產生網頁, 只要套一套現成模板, 輸入內容即可, 而且網路上也可以找到學習資源, 但是也可能因為使用這類工具太“簡單”, 相關的學習資源就沒有我預期的易懂, 所以我花了超乎預期的時間來了解使用Hugo.
下載安裝 可參考網路資源: 1. 在 Mac 上安装 Hugo 2. Hugo 官網
我是透過 brew 下載安裝:
$ brew install hugo  確認安裝結果:
$ hugo version Hugo Static Site Generator v0.42.2 darwin/amd64  建立網站 $ hugo new site MakeWebSite  hugo 會建立 MakeWebSite 目錄, 而且在這目錄底下產生 2 個檔案及 6 個目錄
. ├── archetypes │ └── default.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>