<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English, Guardian on 布萊德的學習網站</title>
    <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/categories/english-guardian/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English, Guardian on 布萊德的學習網站</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 19:20:43 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bradleetw.github.io/categories/english-guardian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[The Guardian] One in five vanilla ice-creams has no vanilla, cream or fresh milk</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/theguardian/vanillaicecreams_0907/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Sep 2018 19:20:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/theguardian/vanillaicecreams_0907/</guid>
      <description>One in five vanilla ice-creams has no vanilla, cream or fresh milk Britain&amp;rsquo;s longest heatwave since 1976 has seen vanilla ice-cream sales soar, but a survey has revealed that some brands are sold without vanilla, cream or fresh milk.
Vanilla has traditionally been Britain&amp;rsquo;s favourite flavour but a Which? investigation of supermarket and branded vanilla ice-cream found a number of them were lacking some key ingredients.
One in five of the ice-creams examined by the consumer watchdog had none of the three ingredients shoppers might reasonably expect to find in vanilla ice-cream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[The Guardian] Scotland to offer free sanitary products to all students in world first</title>
      <link>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/theguardian/freesanitary_0906/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2018 09:45:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bradleetw.github.io/englishnews/theguardian/freesanitary_0906/</guid>
      <description>Scotland to offer free sanitary products to all students in world first Students at schools, colleges and universities across Scotland will have access to free sanitary products as part of a £5.2m scheme to fight period poverty.
The Scottish government is the first in the world to make sanitary products available free to all of its 395,000 pupils and students to help &amp;ldquo;banish the scourge of period poverty&amp;rdquo; - when girls and women struggle to pay for basic sanitary products on a monthyly basis, significantly affecting their hygiene, health and wellbeing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>